I can't believe you called me up.
You're so cute.
I'll be good. I'll be good. I'll be good.
I wish I could do that to you.
The ultimate professional idol is
Because you're Airi
You're perfect and a liar
You're a genius idol
What a god
Sayoshi Onishima and
Airi Suzuki's
Aniverse god song
All the covers won!
What's the situation?
Hi, I'm Seishi Ishima, the talking shit glasses of the ani-song world. And...
Lies are love that only comes once in a lifetime! I'm Airi Suzuki.
The famous phrase of the girl I'm guessing. She doesn't even resemble my favorite anime.
Oh no. I was aware of the lack of resemblance.
I was aware of it, but I put my heart into it.
But when you said that phrase, does it mean that there are other guessers besides Ailee who will be there today?
I love everyone in the world, but it seems that my favorite girl, the girl I really love, will be there.
I see.
And this time, I would like to mention that Irie and I will be doing a cover duet with Oishi.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be dressed like this.
Well then, let's make an announcement.
Seino!
Tuning Love!
Certificate!
Can you sing this?
Are we okay? We are.
After this, I'd like to sing it with erudition.
It's pretty bad to have this on without any sense of humor, isn't it?
Yes, it is. That's for sure.
It's a can-do self.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Now, this time we have this person here with us.
Koan girl!
She's looking a little strange.There's something wrong with you, isn't there?
I'm Yui Sakurai, in charge of mint green at Fruit Zipper.
Pleased to meet you.
Sakurai Paan!
What is it?
SAKURAKURI PANG
What is this?
This is a tribute to Irie's costume from her live video.
I have seen it before, I have seen it.
I've seen it before.
I love her so much.
Every time I saw her, she would cry so hard that the staff would worry and bring her a box of tissues.
He was so worried about me.
I think you are the best in the idol world.
That's right.
The two of you seem to know each other.
That's right. I wonder if they take TikTok together.
I saw them on TikTok.
I saw it, I saw it.
Maybe I didn't hear what you said. All I could see was his face.
That's right. I wasn't in view, was I?
Maybe, maybe not.
From the first greeting, all I could see was my face.
That's right.
It was so cute, wasn't it?
It's hard not to get the word out, you know.
That's true.
I was like, "What do you want me to do, too?
He came to the front of the stage like this.
I'm going to say, "What's your name?
What! Seriously?
During the live performance.
That's right. It's the part where you say it to one person.
What kind of seats do I have to have to be able to see what's going on in front of me?
Well, I'm about number 2.
Number 2, huh?
Then, may I ask you to do nani nani as if you were in the second row?
I'm so happy!Glad to hear it!
Yes, I am.
I'll be there.
Hey, what's the call?
You're so cute!
I called for you!
Cute!
They're gonna do this with the picture from here.
Oh, my God!
Oh my God,
I'm shaking my head.
Oh, my God.
See you later, Ailee.
I'm going to like what you just said.
You want to hear it, don't you?
I want to hear it.
I'll go.
Hey, what's the call?
That's cute.
The camera's moving too fast.
Hey.
You're so cute!
You're so cute.
What is it? Are there any other cute poses?
I think the most popular pose among fans is the one like this, where she's rubbing her hands together.
What is that?
If I did it, my arms would be shaking.
Blah blah blah.
Why was it so cute?
You were malicious, now.
Blah blah blah blah.
Why did you react so fast, now?
Great!
My favorite girl!
Yes! A little man-baby!
That's right.
Aren't there a lot of active idols who are pushing for Oshiko?
Yes, they are. My friends around me are all watching it.That's right. I have a lot of friends around me who are watching it.
By the way, who is your favorite character?
My favorite character is Ruby.
Ruby-chan!
Ruby is the one who practices singing and dancing hard,
I was really impressed by her singing, dancing, and practicing hard.
Who was your favorite?
I'm Ai-chan. It's Ai-chan.
Ai-chan.
Let me talk.
You like Ai-chan?
I've always loved you, Ai-chan.
Who do you like?
I'm Alima, Kana.
I'm so frustrated. They say, "You're so cute!
Also, you know what else? The songs are good, too.
What kind of songs do you have?
YOASOBI's Idol and
Oi's last beat.
No, no, no, yes, there are a lot of open-ended ones in these cases.
So you knew me?
Yes, yes, I did. I have been watching this show for a while.
I thought, "Oh, you wrote this song.
I'm glad, I feel like I'm finally a moderator.
I am very happy. Thank you very much.
I saw Airi sing this song on this show, this idol of mine.
It was really good, watch it. Thank you very much.
What is it, God?
What is that? Do I smell like Kim Jong-gon? I knew it.
By the way, we asked you in advance what you thought was great about this idol.
I was asked in advance what I thought was great about this idol, and I was told that the responses were more enthusiastic than I had expected.
Wait a minute, this is written down in seconds.
Wait a minute, is this written down by the second?
How many seconds here, how many seconds there, and so on.
Like, "13 seconds into this cool song.
There are videos like this in the comments section of YouTube, aren't there?
There are those.
You know, the ones where you press "time" and it takes you there.The one that jumps there when you press time.
It's amazing.
I heard that you have a VTR of the best part, so may I ask you to do a live commentary?
Live commentary, yes.
First of all, the part at zero minutes and 13 seconds.
This is a cool tune, and I think it's a great point that we could see Aimi, the idol, at this moment.
What? I'm embarrassed.
What's embarrassing about it?
Even if you are nervous, just looking at it makes you nervous.
That's what I like about it.
First? There's more.
I like this part first, and I like it from the very beginning.
You mean the way he does this and the way he makes his facial expressions?
It was just for a moment, but it was so perfect.
Thank you.
Do you ever do this kind of stiff-teasing?
It's embarrassing. I'm going to turn it into a big analysis contest. It's embarrassing.
Let's go on to the second one.
The second one is at the 2 minutes and 5 seconds mark.
The mood of the song changes and Airi links the lyrics to the song.
That's the real love.
The media that makes you smile with your best smile
Only this secret that I hide from you
I'll spin it with the lie that I love you
That is my own kind of love
Even the sweat that flows is beautiful aqua
this eyelid that hides the ruby
I'm Maria, I'm Maria, I'm Maria, I'm Maria
That's my kind of love
the media that is the movie order of the peculiar, it's all written down that if you want to divide the human race, you must love it.
I'll only keep this secret that I'm trying to hide, I don't care if it's deceptive
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
I have one line of feedback. It's in the questionnaire.
I've been saying this at home all day... with my hands of love. I know, right?
The pause at the end...
The pause is like Ai Hoshino's.
That's true.
It's like she respects anime.You have a great respect for animation.
I always felt that you came here because you have done a lot of research.
I'm always thinking about it.
You're making me cry.
I'm so embarrassed.
Wenite, I was waving it next to you.
I hope I didn't disturb you.
I was fine with that background.
Ai-chan's background.
I think this is the background.
Who's the background
And just as you seem to be after all these years, I noticed it.
Let's take a quick look.
When you were in elementary school, did you have a hobby of intuitive copying of dances on YouTube?
That's right.
I'm not sure how that led me to become an idol, but I'm not sure how it leads to Airi Suzuki.
I used to do YouTube dance copying after school at my house, and that's when I teamed up with AkB,
I was doing kan-kopi on YouTube at home after school, and I saw Airi Suzuki in a single person's video.
I was really swamped when I saw it.
I saw it and was really swamped.
That was the fateful encounter in the first year of junior high school.
That's right. A fateful encounter.
I thought, "This is what it means to be an idol.
What attracted you to them?
First of all, the level of performance was high. Too high.
They could sing and dance, and they had cute smiles.
Don't film me. It's embarrassing.
I thought, "This is what it means to be an idol," and that's when I started auditioning because I wanted to be one.
That's when I started auditioning.
That was the moment when my image of idols became solidified.
I was very happy to tell her that I was an idol.
I'm so happy to tell him.
What?
The moment when my image of an idol was solidified was when I met Airi Suzuki.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad to be able to say that.
Next, here is Airi Suzuki when I was feeling discouraged.
So you were accepted as a member of an idol unit, and you passed the exam, but it was a group of girls who were already active in the entertainment industry, and who could already sing and dance.You were accepted as a member of an idol unit, and you were one of the girls who had already been in show business and could already sing and dance.
I had no experience, so there were times when I didn't know what to do.
How did you overcome that?
I learned from watching Airi.
Did you have any references?
I had never sung or danced before, so I didn't know how to stop and make a face.
There was a video that I saw repeatedly for the first time that shocked me.
That was Bouno's music video.
My Boy
The part where he sings "Tata Tata Tata My Boy"...
He looks forward with "ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta".
When he decides to go for it, his eyes are full of power and his face is well defined.
By making a decision there, you can make a decision.
You can say so much with your face, can't you?
That's right.
Then, can you actually do it?
I'm going to do it like this with my hands.
Ta ta ta ta ta my boy.
He's cute.
But it's very powerful.
The "ta" here...
I was so surprised to see Airi Suzuki!
The way you turned around.
Amazing!
I wonder if it was me.
It was like meeting a doppelganger for the first time.
Next is this.
I am and always will be Airi Suzuki.
What? Am I going to die?
I still like Airi Suzuki even after she joined Fruit Zipper and got her big break.
Yes, I do. I will never waver. This is the one thing.
Since I became a member of Fruit Zipper, I have had more opportunities to be seen,
So I have more opportunities to be seen as a professional idol.
And I think that Airi is the ultimate professional idol.
So your goal has always been here.
That's right. I really love Airi Suzuki from her ℃-ute days,
I also love Airi Suzuki after she went solo,
Thank you very much.Thank you.
I feel like I'm going to cry.
I haven't cried once when you haven't cried in my presence.
But I don't know, I haven't reached that ideal at all.
I'm not satisfied with myself yet.
We have to run together like this.
That's great. I'm the only one thinking about Yurigo.
Now, as I mentioned at the pre-meeting, there's something I'd like to ask Airi Suzuki to do for me.
I'd like you to take a checkerboard picture with me.
What kind of pose would you like? A pose. With a heart.
What are you going to do with your hand? Nothing.
Cheese.
If you can do the pose, you're doing great! You're so good!
Oh, my God!
Isn't this so good? It's so good!
This is amazing! Give me the side. Side, OK, got it.
I'm totally a staff member.
Here we go. Here's the cheese.
Wow, you two are so picturesque!
Since we're here, let's take a selfie of the three of us.
Here we go.
Yoo-chan, wouldn't you prefer to be in the middle?
I'm even good at taking selfies.
I want one of these.
Let's take another one. Let's take one more.
Let's make it three.
Here you go, cheese.
Yes!
I'll ask my sister to choose one for me later.
I'm so happy!
Wait a minute.
Um, we're out of film.
Next is this corner.
Isn't that the cover of Sakuran-yui?
So cute!
This time, we conducted a survey on anime songs that we want Yui to sing.
This time, we asked Yui to sing a song that she sings as a reference for her facial expressions.
Hmmm...giggling
Cute.
It's an ani-song god song in the mode that he was using as a reference for facial expressions, etc.
Ani-song song
Is it a subject character type, then?
Yes.
Yes, it is!
Here are the results!
Wow, I'm so happy with any of them!
In case you're wondering, last time it was 1st, 2nd, and 3rd singles!
In order from the top.
Now, from among these paper 3 chosen
Yui will cover the following
The ending song of the main character
It's the real me!
I'm so happy!
Is there any reason why you chose this song?
When I hear the word "anime song," the first thing that comes to mind is Bono.
So you are already copying the song, aren't you? Probably.
I've been watching him for a long time.
All the time?
Yes, I was watching him the whole time.
And to sing it in front of you.
I'm shaking my head, wondering if I'll ever do such a thing in my life.
Are your comments the same as Kyutaro's?
And this time, Ailee, I, and Oishi are the duet man.
I completely forgot about it.
I heard that you have a request.
I would like you to sing the ending song, "Turing Love," from the anime, "A Science Guy Fell in Love and I Tried to Prove It.
Thank you very much.
Turing Love.
Hey, hey, hey, I got it.
No stupidity, no stupidity.
I'll do it.
Why this song?
Because of this dance.
I thought it would be super cute if Ailee danced this dance.
I really wanted to see that.That's what he really wanted to see already.
I'm so sorry.
I was able to listen to some of Mr. Oishi's music.
Thank you very much.
I really like the pop feeling of your music.
I'm really looking forward to today.
Thank you very much. It's like a follow-up that you just had to have.
It's true.
Really? Thank you very much.
Please listen to this.
Turing Love with Masayoshi Oishi and Airi Suzuki.
The real me with Yui Sakurai.
You son of a bitch, my real self.
Come out, you're hiding.
Turing Love.
It's only a dream.
One piece map.
Now let's reveal Max Fee Day.
Maidel, Maidel, ok, ok, ok, nice, nice, nice.
Sorry, they know.
It's coming.
They know.
So, in return.
The four little stars are arranged in the shape of diamonds on a playing card.
I feel like I'm in this metanium.